<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
- espace = &lt;br&gt; 
- < = &lt;
- > = &gt;
- & =  &#38;
- ' = &#39;
- " = &#34;
-->
<languages>
    <English>
        <string name = "SpawnMove">Welcome aboard ! &lt;br&gt;I am &lt;b&gt;A&lt;Tutorial_Bot&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, your training robot. &lt;br&gt;First of all, move with &lt;b&gt;WASD&lt;/b&gt; to the table.</string>
        <string name = "Id">Aarning : without the &lt;b&gt;Identification Card(ID)&lt;/b&gt;, yo can't open any doors. Always keep your &lt;b&gt;ID&lt;/b&gt; with you !</string>
        <string name = "Equip">Equip the clothes on the table by getting it with &lt;b&gt;left click&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;br&gt; and equipping it with &lt;b&gt;E&lt;/b&gt;."</string>
        <string name = "PdaInId">To take less place in your inventory, you can insert your PDA in your Identification Card by selectionning &lt;b&gt;the latter&lt;/b&gt; and clicking on &lt;b&gt;the former&lt;/b&gt; ! &lt;br&gt;You can also switch hands with the key &lt;b&gt;X&lt;/b&gt;.</string>
        <string name = "Light">It's so dark ! I might lose sight of you, but you can't always interact and especially &lt;b&gt;pull me by right clicking me&lt;/b&gt; and chose your action. &lt;br&gt;You can also toggle the light integrated on your PDA, like as a lighthouse in a dark world, but only on 2m...  &lt;br&gt;No? &lt;br&gt;I don't need one, I'm a robot after all.</string>
        <string name = "Mask">My sensor detect, an irregular amount of toxic CO2 in the next room at west &lt;b&gt;Equip the mask and the oxygen&lt;/b&gt; stocked in the bag, and don't forget to &lt;b&gt;turn your oxygen on !&lt;/b&gt;</string>
        <string name = "NoAir">Be careful, there is a hole in the floor on the next room. You need to be ready : &lt;b&gt;equip the space suit&lt;/b&gt; to protect yourself from the harsh environment, I think the rest of you organically don't appreciate being exposed to the vacuum of space. &lt;b&gt;Objective :&lt;/b&gt; use the items in this room to repare the hole by &lt;b&gt;using the rod on the empty space&lt;/b&gt;, then &lt;b&gt;use floor tile on the scaffold&lt;/b&gt; to build a base tile and lastly &lt;b&gt;use the last one&lt;/b&gt; to finish the floor tile !</string>
        <string name = "Food">Congratulation on completing your first mission ! &lt;br&gt; you have earned a reward:  you can rest here, eat and drink here, just click on the machines and see what they give you ! &lt;br&gt; You can even throw drinks and packaging on the floor, don't worry, I will clean up after you leave." &lt;br&gt;"From now, you can leave the station by south or continue discovering the station. If you have any doubt about what you see, you can do a right click or a Shift click to examine."</string>
        <string name = "FireArm">This is the Firearm Training Ground, you can train your aim and the guns here.&lt;br&gt;Remember to not waste your ammo in real situation !"</string>
        <string name = "Heal">This is a medbay, where you can heal your wounds here. &lt;br&gt;There should be medical care inside the kit !"</string>
        <string name = "Farm">Look at this room ! Here you can farm food, that are essential to survival ! for you who have to eat.&lt;br&gt;Take a seed from the &lt;b&gt;Mega Seed Servitor&lt;/b&gt;, plant it in the &lt;b&gt;Hydroponics Tray&lt;/b&gt; and wait for it to grow ! &lt;br&gt;You can  add water, use the &lt;b&gt;bucket&lt;/b&gt; to add or remove water, the &lt;b&gt;Spade&lt;/b&gt; to dig and move dirt, and the &lt;b&gt;Cultivator&lt;/b&gt; to remove weeds.&lt;br&gt;When the plant has grow, you can take them and not only eat them, but you can also put one in the &lt;b&gt;Seed Extractor&lt;/b&gt; to extract information from the seed !</string>
        <string name = "Evac">It seem like you can leave this place here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thank you for coming, and good luck for your future missions !&lt;/b&gt;"</string>
    </English>
</languages>